Catalog of open source software in the public sector in sweden there are
corresponding versions i i know both in italy and france maybe we'll hear more about that but we're trying to
gather projects that are used by agencies here in sweden and add those agencies here as well
in order to make it more easy to see what alternatives there are out there when considering of procuring or before
Considering
Procuring or before entering
Also with Mood the discussions to this Forum on the Community page of
Ford 8
I
Pajdeg
Kampement
Jag sa Adjö
You are to you going to register and Continue a conversation
That is WhatsApp
Then we should have this annonstavla calendar
Dimension definition 12 seven
Tomorrow we have biggest Mario
Prestige of the City
Magnus Uggla Show
Irish try Swedish
Sweden and curse you to look at
Adams 30 Seconds to Mars We have
Discussion between christianity
Abdi Open skolplattformen gäspar
Är riksdagsledamot för Centerpartiet
Other than that discuss Open open source
Apple challenges
Formel i Gällivare
Andy sista Pro Evolution workshop on lift table
Mio Heaven Knows workshop on Open stands with Open the
And Energy levels of May We have the remote Open the extra Björn Hagström
If you are missing anything here
Höstmiddag
Charity of the Community perils
4 or email
Maria dalhage for myself
I will go down
Schleich
Soap before moving on
I just like to do I pick some Berries like before
From the previous workshops och This is the third Watch app We have an open source
And
Samarbete Charges tap-windows
Talking to people from discussion
Är det kö
Some of these
Mention the lack of guidelines in
How to come to the
Which kind of picked up on the last Workshop
Sand Dunes of the Galaxy
Mig counteract collaboration
Krokoms metodist
Or
Oneplace intresserad saker i glas
Sometimes license can be missing or counteracting
Lack of knowledge
German tank y Messenger
Lesnovski marketing on what open source Software is available
With her a lot of myths and without makeup
And lack of Culture and Processing
Baby
This is just to play some som
Som över alltså Detta pengar till dig
Where to look at High
How other countries are working on this
Supporting and
And improve The General population of work on open source software
Public sector
Have a very Thankful to have
River national
Ica Sävast Daisy
First We were here from Bastian
And how do you do
I know they come a long way and they are really progressing
And also
Safe for Italy and we have a problem
Den
I will have
Rasmus free from movies to talk about
How many Fatalities are working Clary
Danmark
So I have scheduled 15 minutes for questions
India and ovie
Presentation
Jonas HB Trading that part
Danny and we will have a discussion
Open camera
Without Me
Presenter
And with that
I had it all with you fast
Hej
Can you tell me when
Yes
Thank you
Start showing my streaming
Denna
Ok can you see my brother
Can you see my brother I
Yes
Ipad
Lancelot freme
Ambassade algerie
I am free Software activist now working for the french administration
Ring morfar
Enhancing
Everything about free software do we use it to
I will buy it scary BuildIt century
With the rest of the administration
I will try to be quick and interact me Anytime
This is my homepage
Just to remind me that I'm on the Block
Nyköping
I can wait
Twenty years
Get anything that
I am
Well acquainted with the
The large ecosystem of free soundtrack
France
Nadja
Jennifer
Fuck you
Japanese traditional there
I have a kind of girl with the vision by Reading This book
My friend
Kan du öppna Youtube cyber future
Basically
Godisbukett
Individuell
Aktivera missnöjd
Institution
Is the key
When you doing a big change inside
Pizza
Friskvård
Then I tried to Lars institutionen together
Thinking I was asking for this is to be able to make
Dare to make Streets
The we use open source in the world
Äppeljuice
What is programme by the Obama administration
I think WhatsApp
Go
Innovation Fellows breaking
Designer at the scientist and developer Within Gemini station 2 prefixed
So I was right in the Aftermath of the Healthcare
Android
From this program in 2017 from inspiration from this
Staten
The same problem with French administration wish I was lucky
Working for the Ministry
Helping to be
Battery inventory of agents
From where I joined that
Iittala bicicleta missionsförbundet
A indian food last the news
Ja absolut
Ten years anniversary
Reggie Smith
Into promoting Open data in rising of datasheet
Share by organisation
Acciaroli Italy always
Very close to open source but
I was no one in charge for open source
En kille i doing a Tab in 2018 and of the year
ADD
Because
Såskurs
Administrations
Ligg ligg considered to be administrativt dokument
Thanks to the 2016 Law that we have in France
The Body Shop
So I took this Lego
Round Two
Help promote in the fuck
That we need you open source
Messenger
Maybe there people you have on people
Kändisar
Audio Android just a small Team
Nej
Smoking
Pedagog
Byta godis possible for Brewing
A Project Within Janis
Small
A
Jeans
And
I took the hobbits from 2018
15 to open så såldes ost
When you go there on the Project page you see all this new
Public services
Bra old innovativ experiment
Aden have this in common that they opened
Sov gott
This page
You have shatri
And you can see that the whole Squad
Ekosystem
The Last Five Years
Iittala
Pedagog
Änkepension
The habit of Being yourself from the very beginning
De har gjort av de nu
Why the central Digital
Administration
Show that
Things like a infrastructure for Network infrastructure for the world
Minister
When I first try to
Make the best role Models since this mission was
Well known Japanese version
Decided to make a list
That we that we are open source that we drop
Side
Oslo dörrlist
This is just a basic madam
Order free software
Conceived using
Lat
Så
Not Ready to make the division med rest
Promote Where you singing
Where
And at the same time
The new
Indica the time 2018
What also starting to get
I wish Bass on Ellen
The Free software
Visa Netflix på TV
Big National Pride
Konsum the Lights On
Open source Airport
Isak
The Success We have
Modernt
100000 skisser
Hur mycket ginseng
Okej inspiration and
Even though not all them know this is a Frost
Open sosefo
Jag är Key open source
Project from a this central administration
Is the Marshall plexi
Which is the key tool for digitalisation
Bomb
Indian Mistress
So we developed this from within the new
H2O det att mista känns inte ens mål administration
Local agencies
Ende Judith
Ur
Dimma tröja Lies down
Procedure
Success and now they
Jim ishockey Simon central administration
Thanks for the
Thanks for the Software being open source There is another thing
Dissa sin plattform
Kul att kolla
Now
Zoo
Illustrious
We've been putting your efforts
Basically in2it
First one is to promote Old Open software
Published by the
Sorry we have to
Simply make list of all the Beach Club and Birgitta
Agoni
Sushi accounts
Red Bull
Den from det
Listing all repositories
Väder where to find
Here
Albin selecting the beta golf
Organisation
Pedagogiskt sadist
Organisation Dublin
Present
En fantastisk byta god organisation I can't see the list
Ja precis 3 you can solve them
Spider
Number of views
That's the guitar
Öppna universum
Already
Thanks
Here is some small feature that we want to and hands and neck
Twitch
Organisation you can have
The list of dependencies
So I took inspiration from
Project Bachelor
Open Collective
And we try to harvest dependencies for older repository
Review
Insights into
What is the
Organisationsteori
Baby one of the most used dependency for a
Anthem
Eggens i Sandviken Hafa
Det känns
Using all the
Ecco2k
Using a man Imagine Dragons
Frontier
And we want to make something of a decision
Need to make this interface more useful
End to end a line What is
Origin interesting and useful for
Everyone
What has a degree of generic
Just for you not for everyone
Show me into this
Information and write you
Try to grab WatchMojo
Everyone and to promote
Line of duty
You have Japanese version Open their Souls
Wemake
Är Lego
Interactive website
Play min Audi
In what case to have to open in what Keys to have to take care of Possible secrets
Possible personal data within the source code in Sundsvall
Basically this kind of India to website
Are you Selling
The can say that question to Ace
And read the Lord with you
You have you can see you have links to specific part of the road That may be ready for you
Änden
Jens I have the list of things
The definition of you
Nytt publisher software
And you have to select a penis i flies
Contact someone is something is here if you have
Questions
And when you contact someone on the email contained information
This platform is
I sleep with it to your needs
Megascan of interactive
Website
Eyeonid
I Just Died using a bug down
Konfigurera
Gais
That we try to be
Activate
Transport
Questions on how to
Exposure svenska
One of the main questions We have
People are afraid of Open the source code is gonna be like Wikipedia anyone will be about
Snösko
99 % of the source code that
Published by Gert minsta kändis transparency reason
Vad är fission
Sims work more efficiently when they work in Japan
But very few of them open to receive contributions
Wink Rage Project to be Berry clear bag
Expectations
If you Ed blevo means that You Are lyrics
Nobody
Expect from you
If you are the sea level
Publishing That's why
Get
This is something we have to explain
Så där va du first Iphone
When the fuck is on
Protean Why is there What is a republic and
Encouraging administration Swedish law
Jag dör per år Focus is this catalogue of free software
Diplo
Spiderman
Company
And that we can create a meditation to use
Odyssey tomorrow
Efficiency and respect for that respect The Path of
The Free Software Within Destruction because
It's been there all a
Eniro
Reflex
Du först
Intent
Was to let central administration review the same free software
Find that too many different
Words on using the same Solution for of Central
Agnes
I have also because of the time administration start the experiment with buying Instagram
Arkiv
Bass software
Baby one two three Dimensions but not for Old versions of the street
Addis airport to MB converter
Tova
Secure
Visions of the free software
En en bajskorv
Ingenting
Today
Weed
See things differently
It's funny to comments both mysql and Maya The Bee
Är det konstgräs i VM
Will you have to tailor
Biztalk meditations to your needs
Zoe
This catalog is larger and launcher
And we tried to make deeper
And you want to contact someone
If you see Solution Here you want to get more information
Solution you have this Linkin
Vampire City kontakt
Because behind this There is a network of 100
Open 60
Hejsan
Jens
Deploy
Så får jag bli din
Wixy
Desmos
Katalog
Amma
Two minutes
Recently
And I was the coming back the first Mystery 2 Philip
Är du full
Varför finns du
Asking to
Where Are We Now about Open date
Specifically window
When it comes to
Open source in the source code from the
Wizzair
Viktor
Så
You have the weather
Member
Missions to
Gather all the inspections from the public administration
Add to America
Reports on These questions of opened Ida and open source Within
Adda
Jag vill ha
And this report recently made
Sovrum
Sensor
Back in december
The report makes this important recommendation
Having open source program Office
Anything But
And also using open source widget in distress
Stating that
You need to have single strategy
How to avoid
Disconnect between
Musical.ly syns
Zingo
Silikonspray
Medicin
Publishing
Bye
Battle for me We are in this
Wear this open source program Office SBM design
Dialog With Many organisations are not just the administration but also
Honda Civic
Right now
What's important
It's you
Consider the world ekosystem
Johan from the administration
And one outside of
Jennifer Chanel chance We have Francis to have this very Active Ski
I mentioned the road
Of a
De marzo
Lead Natalie by the central administration
Also by disassociation Abdullah
Paris
Hosting the source code for many local agencies that drops
Energy Light That been a kiss
Processor
Ja
Extending the strategy of the central administration for the local
Nypozin
Finally just World on the method
ÖB
Samurai into words
Connect
The last two years of
Anneli ben
What is already there and that Nobody will see
Så bra någonting What use that
What is published by
Promotech
Adda
Agents that experts
Din tur
Some free Software open source software
That just that way
Iden Indien
Kingdom and
Tinder
The Second World connect is already about this
Uploading this Networks of people with no
Happy Together
Finally That's the wall
Idé Behind Blue hat
Brewhouse
Yngve Dree Low
Cs:go
Is anyone who is interested in
En frisör
The intersection
Public interest value
Free software
People from the administration
Also anyone outside of Germany station but
Who is protected in Gemini
We have this big Association in France
Amazon
Jag provar
Visa square and sometimes 3-series for teacher
Hanna sak
Isak player in this Direction
And
Så ja trying to build more events in Bluetooth
Albin Kajsa Ring for the last ten years
Modern the workshops online
And I will Continue to make that in this Direction
Connecting and extending the
Thank you I am done and ready for
Thank you for a presentation
Ring till gjutjärn
Are you there Jonas
Så kan ju hinna
Yes
Sazerac
Annika Madsen är question in the chat here in the beginning
Some problems Johan
And one of the question Is How
Bastion have
Teknos problem exempel One of samothrace dimension
Culture
Magnusson
Måste
Working Club Ring open source
Questions to Bastian How are you tackled
Culture and the mind setup
Working Class
Nej
We try to
Give examples
En also We are very careful not to propagate
Turn the Lights On open source
Asteroids
People
Glutenfri kolla Breaking The Try to build a great
Adidas
That's Linux
That's Maybe Firefox that
Summer key price
Omni projects Sometimes you have just a few mandenius
How many projects sometimes
You have this one Company behind the Project
And
Hamburgare Solna
Real forced this a sign of the times
Exclude something
Sometime
When I die speech
People
A level of decision Makers in Japanese
I want to distinguish
Fake and true open-source
Kinguin
Becoming it is and becoming a genius
Empirical
Igen
Come to my mind
En fake open source There is okay Where is one Company with great Project
Bad luck
Blocks in the same if you you this opens Brother then you gonna be like in with this
Nice things about computers
Altrincham
Benzos just about the licenses
And the availability of the Project
Whether you start from a situation where you have a community Where you start for machine when you have
Company
The Mother that the license use anyone the chance to enter the Dark
Anyone
Is my mother
Within This is the amazon elasticsearch
Messages in other contexts 2
So
I tried to
Som vi liksom på That's the way
We talk to the Future change the battery
Birgitta
That's the
Give examples of
Daisys
That's what I stand for
There is nice use case
AFA
All the regional National Park
Getting Together to build a single
Kenneth
Good example
And
Brixtol lights into Blue examples and two
Nationell institution
Into the treaty define what they expect
Open sourcing
Berry
No Expectations live
Expect to have better documentation
That's very nice
If you expect you have more contributions I just nothing but very nice
Weather
License
Jason Scott
Vad är Into the Wild
Do you have any questions
Låt som en rosett service
Keep on Cosmic prisons in the There will collect and which language best young and old
Ulltäcket from from the nothing
Okej
South at presentation
Then we are moving over to
Hur många about the great country in the South
Italy
And
To you
Var är Christina Schollin
Jäst
Thanks
So alone
A Good morning today
Briefly About The Shining striving for conference that before
Can you give me a little bit of introduction by
What are we doing now please
Hörde Badass av
Speaking of the Digital transformation team ever since January
Bikini bikini
Så
It'll be more Stable right now So give me stream
Games like
Seven days ago
We have
Ministre Ministries
I national anthem
Sorry now I have a pie monitor Stable
Devoteam is going so I will briefly explain you with
Parodier 2017 before and right now we're doing
Esport of the garment in the Deep
So
I really wish
Have a very low talking about a friend open source
This is några You So this is Ben
True since many years ago just
Quickly go through the three main
Malmslätts a of this transition
Störningen 25
Slayer
Setup dislodged
Code for the colonisation where
We started to see
The idea of reviews
So oskuld directly using a public administration
White Wire new software
En scout and Chuck
For all the Possible Solution Digital Solutions available the other public administration
Music chords
Ådi
Build and you and
Kontakta administrationen
Permission to use that
Sideways of one to one relationship
And a really work now is your name
Play
All of actors For Dummies
Something in 2012 that primary lower belly chain
So they introduce just latest interview
Via open source so I started to think about three years in 2012 where
Whenever a public administration is the Wire a new piece of software
Hair stopper open-source over på Bright i så fall
So you know
SingStar to banan
Experiment and Whistle something that working something that was not working
Weather in 2016 the big change
Roger in the same Row the same code
We see how the world's end
Move and merge
Står were talking about you use it when you for talking about the pictures 2012 however in place
Youtubers merch Android
Where can
Torka bär och juice
If Only
We have open source open source is the only way you on a
A new Solution
Used by another emission release by now
Så okej Så little step by step Pricerunner
We arrive appen till Nowhere
We have been struggling Place everything seems to be shining and also
Weather wizard
From 216 to 2018 nothing really change
Because you know when you have a primary Low
It's something written Somewhere in very high level turns in
Billiga linser
Very Handy for the
Developers for the Republican Illustrator that has to understand what this is about
That's why
We started to tacos på sig okej
Build a situation one hour good very well
Samwise
Work in this way What can we do to solve the Trials of this disease
So thats Why Im 2017 2018 starting to draw
What is right now called the guidelines and acquisition and Reeves
Public enemies
Which
A document is basically translating the same reload into something more
Into some guidelines into some practical
I know meme
Action The everybody can I sleep I can I Sleep well too
Vill du bajsa på dig
Don't mean that we die
Set in to the Framework of the guidelines
I said we are having a central caldoso
I know one of the biggest questions the Everyday comes from body condition is okay the losses
Go look for answers after the Lost
Look for
Chapter Made by other public administration and
Released astromancer Where do I find a song
Han is not so easy for for them to understand
Innerdörrar samma plattform Sounders
Meny
Software-as-a-service
Repositories engineer with organisations in So that's why Will
Hoverboard
So angry
What does a publisher have to do when have a They have to acquire a new please
Solution osdp amarillos
The first step is to make a comparative assessment They have to make an evaluation
Dr2
All the while and I have to check all the Possible Solution
Of course they up to
There Is it again before The Thrill of it all over the license one of the favorite
Golden League prize money
Wednesday
Decide that the fundamental Solution or Not
Det är något fel
Beijer to specified and motivated reasoning over
Pretender
Zombies have to be signed by the administrator Say Hello
We made the comparison with Navy a Body and Soul
Solution is Somehow better than the other
Jag stod i Marieberg
And if the public administration design There is no Software available
The feel the need
Bendy can decide to build a soccer from scratch however that piece of that has to be
Description in the law has to be
Released a******
Which free open source light
Lyssnar du på mig
Instead I like to
Thunderman 2
Ntex plane of the
Let's quickly see how the moment face to the
Visa with talking you before is working a needs to
Bilduppgift Saturday och Nämdö
Gå in på ecb commission The Software to a third party
Job and the job assign ownership of Everything
Imitation of the Possible
Phone is the work
Back to the public and has the owner
The Public administration Following the guidelines Boliches is open Torso
Golden Palace
Everything on tobacco speedball
Eddie
Varför is automatically registered by the Developers and then I will see how this girl is
En bild
Så visade dem en Facebook
The real Space again
Is made Possible by Thanks to the colour me in the Developers Italy calixo
Bubblegum i station B
Mastering Somehow similar to be away so before the First windelius
Do is go on top of Developers Italia overpowering national
After
Search for the tsar
Indiskt search face
The Public administration find the Imago Software The Wonder weeks before That was made by public
So what is what
Administration Beanie to do is not a Constructor 198
Necrodancer tried so I can go
Into the Forest
Independent download de som käket Dustin
Doing
We can do whatever we are used to do with
Är skillnaden Solution with mine
Everyday On The Web
Whenever
Be understand dödsoffter mig Somehow feat
Some of the Creator ok
It's Easy just download 4K if you a if you wish
Änden
Of course you may need to be to build something Dark Souls just change the logo change
Something are some Strings and text
Car and engine
Customize ideologies for your own interests
What does it mean
I m
Where are you download
It's yours Now it's you play it's your Four
You know that work and then you a point då ska ta Michelle waterboarded
Third party developer does whatever you do
Dans i customization Just for
Dustin
Bild player sonntag
Baby without building overload
En printscreen
Agent or this customization are assigned the ownership of the customization
Sandback
Public administration
Basically does the same Jobs before so
Leif Gustav mission
En Publishing
Open
Zoezi
The Two Faces are very similar because
Whenever
We have a devilment whenever we need
Build episodes after Then that
Visa from the ownership of this after goes back to the min station
Ändra min station publishers
If it from scratch is okay
If I can a customization there's something really exist before
Egen pizza
Of course
Enzo Something in the chat before about Grown Up stream
This is very important so agender guidelines Tell
Whatever it all step on this
New repository
Så det customization or the baby deportees or whatever you of Me
Maybe
Om det är ju inte ditt fel
Can go back
First
Upstream showbiz upstream cycle is really
Specified in the guidelines and Will I push forward administration 2 closest
Okej Sorry not web
8078 + 8
We would like that
And the main
Where can we push upstream sauternes demerts
Antar på de originala avstängd
Has to be there so we can talk about it
So Brooklyn review
Developers Italy before
Dive into it
Bay Breeze Uddevalla precis Alla is first and foremost a kommun
I like to call them a community of the lovers Even if you're not all Developers
Public enemies videos
Pro player Zodiac
People please
Private Company
IMDb The Old join our communication platform
And a
I like to save the day build the Digital public Services Together the crab rave
Someone writes after Someone writes I know
To find requirements someone else is a casting them so it's a good can you
Dubai brunch
Ja the particulars and of course Is Everything That is written is released as resource
Play license season and Willis Demons up on
On our
Ring Siri
Of course the opposite Alicia is
From the web
Okej Frontline Kinguin
Guidelines
The opposite of Is there a place where the catalogue of fine pictures of Shrek is
Alexis
Så
Before and before These nationalisation sig of the of the
Plattform
We have
Many many people Club raining again using the forward for of course
Form.io people communicate with some communication Channel
Where is 6000 people like so we offer
Many to many
Possibilities for people for citizens for Gaming station interactive
Puss
We can talk alarm
Built - Me To Be A community of practice me too
Good together the people write code with People that are The Users in this case working with public administration
Power Users
Bearingpoint
Two of them on the same table and make communication
Let's Let's quickly see how this is Bill
We so different than before our
Karaoke
Silverlit saying someplace
So
We want to be
Hjärnan är bara decently
So we the one
Bubblegum I Swedish design is the code to innocence and something
Has to be updated maintain over again
Want to be as much on
Decentralized
The Guardian
Tell The Public administration and wizardry for to put their code on top of Korra avsnitt
Änden
Whenever they do this process they don't get the code by the food 15 danisco
Public piano
En bit file is made of this so I can dream it You can see over here very
Nikotin sallad med det där är Destruction of God
Imagine you
A cold fasting without an organisation for your own music
And then you have inside organisation a lot of
Reaper is it repository contains
Säga Software There is a program for service
Inside That
Codecademy
Together with in the room
Other people Siri use when you another file discodräkter can explain
Very briefly What the Software is this
What do you do in with Developers there in I will go round with Pro Adobe
Sodastream platforms and look specific
Infällda
Code will look for the public
I find it with quality and environmental Destruction information from the Fallen
Stäng formationer controversy
Så jag kan säga vad du heter
Amberry
This is there exists try Now it's called increment
And you can't see this all this information so the name The categories
The screenshots the links and the index of the Valley
Meaning house
How many actions have been
Gynnade maintainers of the
Colder Speed on dubbdäck
ATG repository in the last
Puritan
So
Orbeez information i form and restricted from the public and publish
Sorry now in the first Half a first year of the color we see that we have 66
Public administration the Earth starting to use
We have 200 there now that be with you
Newlywed 1800-tal
Show We're slowly sing the best method is
Definitely work in More
Way more than the method
Existed before Suicide Squad for the directory
Drive now
Public administration are
What's a more
Janet / efter to release
Officer studentbilder and I really
There are more Independent in doing this because they know that
Other people and Other public administration
Around Can we use
Those pizza water without
Closing after som det
Without asking them
How to build a how to install Without You med dig micro SD
Makeup organizer
Menti.com fork and Miguel
Customization double and One Direction
Who is the changes Back to The Roots dinner and try to my
So you know this is nothing new price
Itzhak Howdy
Normal trees after work
Word
Foreigner work for many years
However
Sebastian Tony for the den
Big stepper is the really
Explain B
Mekaniskt disapproves this methodology in the public administration World
SOS working Wayland
Not so straightforward for them to explain how
These are frisör the world war
Så att
We are the infinity
Learn some Lessons in this Industry in the last three years
First of all
Det är det public administration turn on
Elias Tommy forward 8
Bayram 2019
Small Wonder Youtube
It's really difficult to
2 Pro
All of them in the Same Way
We try different in different approaches and Wizard and work and some Really don't work
Linda
Some cases
Folksam with little Bear Little movie Police
There is to go to the following
Vid
Description
Everything day Guideline pulso
Most probably the need to upgrade before so we need to find
Some centres of Competence on the territory 2
Grounded find older requirements of the difference police and then together
Acquires there I can build a bridge and publishers
This is different for big administration has killed on the Powers died in
To go on the phone
Bilder
Release
Follow the work Flow in Independence
Om det inte comparative evaluation of selling for it Break It nice it
The latest later nine years ago Sorry to introduce decided
However She has to be a simple graph
Sometimes with effect
So the reaction of the public administration is that Okay way
More difficult and just you know Going the
Lindenytt
Fuck you anyway so
Why should I do this and how do I do this is better if it's very easy Gold a One
Så
Our mission right now on this year will have this problem is to make that
Spasiba
Indycar lägga shortnin you before is
Dagens Industri
So they just gonna look for some keywords find the afternoon the
Vivaldi
And then this point is really really important thing Alone
I heard many many member states in other countries around the world
Pushing forward in the law Directions I want a Loaded Forces
User reviews and publishers out in the public musician
Dark Norrnäs
You have to provide to this web developer and doing now
What is our Mission to provide Tools right training
Denform community song
Forms date and shine how to make sure I will inform i dance on the territory
Able to do that again I will inform
Men då lastningen renau BGA spo
Kanske vi kan ju basware We heard it everywhere
Please If you're going in that Direction be sure that
Competencies
So we want to create a lot of wecode Emily Kompetenscenter
Where the company That is not so
If you want to build a
Centre de älvsbryggan München
Quiz
Ensure that the content is there is not religious
Creating an other stories structured
Kenneth
Lastlös
Ta in the tourist
Stress my publications
The Only One
Slayer the First
Isa skin
Body commissions to release the car
Showbie
If you follow the law you can
Develop the cold Energy and of the processes For everything
Innan innan open-source
What I would like to see is
Organisations Go
Open by Design The Very first come the very first
Even Before Before starting to develco
Whiplash
On our Farms on our communication channels with administrators to talk with
Kvällspasset
Because we want them to be a friend is transparent Open is possible from the beginning
This really simplifaster
If you start with an open Mind Set a reminder on this afternoon
You have people
Fest that pizza ever leave
Och sen in i fashion Sweden Poland to facility
Delprocesser
Unreal keynan
Pressing a body Don't just think about releasing the after someone die
Think about changing the Minds and going Open by Design from the Bear
First
Visa My
Are my contacts in the bed to take
Thank you for us and presentations wearing Seinfeld
Jonas Do you wanna
Samurais and the question
Jag sa ju det
Oscar One questions for the Thank you doing a lot of remarks and it's really have a lot
Carglass in Italy the same to you
Publish Open nothing
Betong
That always in Sweden
Really good to hear you celebrate a little bit more about that
The Thing
Glory Days in Italy was a prerequisite for your work
Do you think I can
Begagnad Audi
Lost it later this work with open source
Så lite tips imorgon
Baby baby
Wisla was one of the most wanted
So people don't really really Far Away or
Dan wyllie
Malicious to difficult to understand me because it was a little bit you know
Hard to grasp all the details
Open source
So not sure I don't care
Thing The Loan can not so much
En Maybe at the same time the Tools alone Youtube
When do a public administration specialist
Hej
Polygamist readers will I have a lot to compare with a lot of Details
Thanks that
Everyday
They have to make sure baby
Så introducing new lol
In some way Can You See Me
Moreover more more headache
So
Gallon egenremiss dressing on this It's not however
You have low and then you build a famous people with a lot of people
Like
45 before I now but we're going off
That will know what is about
Build Products the build Tools the facility I know the price
That's the tea
So I am not sure Because I didn't leave this
I never in a situation and not sure if this too long can I work
However and telling you the long does it work
Do I need both components to be
Perfectly merge
In order to
I know
Reverend a really want to talk to the public
So that's when they say okay
Thank you
Jobs good we understand now
Weekend på vintern
Naturli
Perfect answer this May experience in the Field so
Ja
Thank You The Lord of the silver bullet
Jag tänkte så så rolig kille
Tack
Five minutes
We also have a very
Nice little friend working France
Natalie download selfies 9 i miljoner
That
Canagan
In my opinion it could also be kontraprodukt
We have a low that says
Administrations ancora
Ljus i Alingsås
Så
This creates a lot of Expectations from companies
Sibylla socialtjänstens
The distance between
Angry and
Station
And empowering this admission to make the right choices
And you have the Internal competencies
Mac destroy season to system
In The Long Run
That's the key
Of doing things rights in the administration
And
And that's the invisible
So
IF by any chance to the civil Society in the activist outside
Ja
Asking for a lot to change into this anchorman switch Sinful
När börjar Aktuellt
Intro
Priority
Hi my Guess is that
IF members of the Parliament We are convinced that we need to have
A priority
Sweden B
In the neck
23 years because we don't have the methodology
Är not This priority with examples
Icelandair inspiring
We don't have the Fullmetal the g2a nap this priority and having Alone
Points into the right Direction but would create a lot of this illusion
My work
Is 2
Try to build the things
In a way that is priority
May be Possible One Day
Discretization
Anthem
We are in the process of Stone
Using Publico
Mormor
And I should stress That is very useful to
Pizza
First Date Was You
Information
Be cool without battery
But now that we want to build Quality Hotel
Vad är recball Directions
Now we have
Enzo
Gemini station weekend
Halvardsson
How to use public Health
Music is experiment
I think I am maturing enough
Does god exist Without Me
Another
Beautiful
Nice
Social work
Open Sonos
Software for research
Hasanovs projector
Melodin kontaktsmitta dejta
The needs for
Är inne
Wizard software
Station
In scientific articles
Så I hope you can align the vocabulary is in the Ski mask
Judisk Nice subsidies bild
So we translated into French
We shall continue
Direction
I hope China
Europe will Someday
Judisk
Yildiz
Thank you for the input
Think we we have a lot
Studio Game by
Johnny
Rfr Send
Baby you see that the public will call wife exempel structure and
Really fine conway's in The Shining
Solskydd that were using and
Lives After that is Used by process
Candy Capital
Samsung Tab skulle kontaktlista
African AC
Thanks for everything for you wish that a bit of discussion
Hitta.se
Question What does
Do I need a lot of it is Ashley
Jag fixar
Baby
Really good
So with that
So we have touched on the original
Aspects and collaboration something That's a great way to move
Rast
Happy
How do you work in Denmark in Times of trouble
Queen
Nintendo switch
Thank you
Black Friday
I don't know if you want one thing with you
What about buying
Showing a great example
Rasmus
Alltså det är Eurovision
Hasse
Collaboration Battlestar in os2
En
What do I say to volunteer members
H&m
Får jag kalla dig sen
Ystad
Founded in English classes in 2012
So Most of the members are
Nej
Lyssnar
Valentino members
What is this thing is grown Audi i tiden
Interview answers
Linda Torsås
Results more more
Kommer om en timme
Älvstranden bra
Magic in the manga song
Understanding cooking interest from other parts of the Page
Show some of the origins and
Cube escape room inspiration
And Other important areas are you sister
Supplier
Irish campingplatser brite the cold and Free
Search
We already know about that can help us
With bar and how is the code That was born to ride
So I have sex
Free buy apartment
Sourcream and chili
When you come to us and astronomie sköldpadda
Godmorgon
Kan du ringa Sara
They do you gonna hand over two hours after what everybody
M
Public sector in Denmark kristendomen
Max riding coat Alice Babs
De hade sin bästa vän
Arbetsliv
Witcher
Super smash game
Call foundation of truth about Cherry
Transparencies tack
Resolution 2
Kommentar från next Thank you next Make It Better
Animerad Open
Sektor
Så roligt med din häst
Snowrider
Specifika stubbar
Charing rate Solutions
Activate
Two Seat problems
Men Dennis about
Gaming control
About the Software Solutions
Taking köra weekend customize in Solution Stewart
Make sure that we have a high degree of influence
Paus
What should I do understand what you
We want to be able to
Reviews hide Will you search Something Good
Michelberger
Thinking in Services so I don't
Instagram
Buss från times party
Ring Josse
Korsord.dn.se
Paus
Ring Vendela Ken
So I can actually be free to use
Bingolotto på soffan
Creature and another one another creature and serving the collection
Reason that
Windows to have decided to
That makes it possible
First year and maintain the control of
Spanien
Vårdcentral
Väder fredagen 2
To your needs and to zero
Messob restaurang
Cute when you are Traveling Across the fuck is xur
R34 the citizens and the companies to be party
Today I know there is
20 + Recall prata
SMS plustjänster
Specific needs English classes
Afterwards Willy's Thassos
En en
Different maturity Levels samma bizarre I Used by
At2020usb 560
So
Seinabo Sey
Supplier
Arbetsinkomst
People make money
Everything Me Everything That's release notes to swedish public license
Impera
Sweden
It's of something for us and use it myself
We want to
Youtube
Punschvisor players in suit Pink
Okej how to wax in the business around Please open Spotify
And we already have you planet
Test Software Solution
Round the Opera Kristianstad
De som pricegain plus Boden
Som alla sa
Skillinge
Making Denmark trackball
Ensam
Unicorn Party
Visa din hustru men vi kan du
Telefon till Nybro IF you change the assistant
Hallå
I samband med lanseringen
Sodastream Drive
Squishy
Samtal Axevalla license på Messenger
Någonting bättre Albin 2020
M m
Overtime ass
Richard Madden 16 Android
Virtue
I swear When We take ownership and when release Discord
We also have to make sure that thing thing thing we have to make sure things are developing
Going in the right Direction Beatles
I going to go
So I have
Merriam last Focus on building up
Nicki Minaj is a round is correct
Round the record
So
We chose to organize this
Support electric palmbussen del
Overwatch fartyg accessoarer
Avicii
Endast en säck 25 kg
Support
Which things together
The Fisherman TuneIn
Party
Try to organize soda can be self contained
Sydkorea
The needs
People making decisions on behalf of this
Musikparad
People making sure that When does the element Minecraft
Pricerunner
Finance
Surprise
If humans were to say something funny
I will make sure that
Technician
People dollar
Jazz of discussing directions to spara Go
Sonic limoncino views of the public administration
Michelle dockery
Visa mig Commitment
Party Casino
Pool och manager
Folksam
Nyheter24
Ja det mesta är klart
Collaboration and Communication Tools
The crimes and the kitchen
Bosch slipmaskin
This is very important for a successful
Open source
Artikel generator
Because have
Restaurang batteriet i level one
Waze
Billigaste culturing parat
How to get to level 2 on level 3
Ali
And
Think
Brown
Little modern house
Nothing that we look at is this Fahrenheit
Minimum requirements Only One
Fury you have on level 3
Men det kostar så mycket
Patrik petreevent tfue
Spela vändtia firepoppy
Inspiration
Maryland International
Vi hörs
Dance for Me things like to mention
Posering
Which tool to use
Ja den pratar inte någonting
Instrument
Back to this one
You need to have that someone called In Between the music
You are sending to have some
Kebnekaise
Units.se
Decision Makers
What is about
Ja så här to take despacito black screen context of National Treasure
Som inte nässpray
You have to take and you can take
Wendie malick
Despacito
Sorry that was a little bit about How nice
Pattex organize
How do I make sure that
Ja men säg inte den där people Axel
Stäng how to Jackson
Standoff
Hallå
Kutcher
Ändra
Basic things that you need
Temperatur 20 %
Festival I need something
Sa Go
Men liksom prästlus
Somewhere I Belong To
Extramile
To make a call
Okay It's of course
Nu är jag en tjej som heter designtips
14 september
Underbara
These people need a good framework
Hello sagemaster15
Panda
Sugar waxing that
Sparkvot
The Square to come to the pick
Trädgård
After work you need to h&m
Starting to show the results
Circle k
Chromecast.com to do something Extra
M
Class of the wild Wind Direction
Dianshiju
El Cielo
Corren
Embezzle
People can say that
Taxi Vallentuna
Extra mile i Vällingby
17000 front and
Mixers something
HBO
Someone intro
Using the results but today
M
When you combine The Streets
Danish games of Everyday
So
Ali västerbottenpaj Just walking around
Det var kul
We need to be able to jump around
Very easy
SSO
Nicolas Berry and
Print structures
Ecosystem
To come around in the sunshine and I need someone from the Interest
Intro
Entusiasm
Det är sommar
Created this organisation
IF read More
I don't have a corner
No anteckning
Det som kommer
Glass
Eurostar
The correct way
Chairman of you have heard
When I wanted to
Project and goodies
O'Learys i with somebody Starstable
Then someone accidentally
No it's something that you are not allowed to create Software in the public interest and give away
Alliteration
And We Know
Bajsa
Okay Most of the time
Total supply
Viva Hofors
Many There is any Doubt
We have the Season 3 of you go through
If you thank you in Japanese
Cancel Something in the Law
Säg inte att du kan inte
Slackline Most of Time you're not living in the Moonlight
And then you can sell your likes
Gillar du spirella20
SOS sida
If you want to
Something
The common interest and that you want to watch the Mandalorian
I need to read from the start
Pacific create a Solution of the Aftermath
Alltså paprika
Johanna
Linda
Dispute med lite papper
Loppisar på Youtube
Questions
Answer
And
Vårdcentralen Barkarby
Connect me to play Funky
Thank you for a great presentation
Henning Witte Jonas
Yes
Presentation
I will try to travel say that låter precis surround
To me I will presentation be published so I will publish the presentation of the words I wanted
Så fick westerblom Peter Krantz
Bendy reaction of the damned is closed source Software industry
Men det har inte kommit till som vid OS 2 Pro
En
Sum-sim from.the
Aitik companies the don't have incitament directory
Ago the open Huawei
Inte riktigt samurais
Discussion in the chat
Try to complete Sweden we have
Storytel We have one last night You come to k m g
Nothing Just give local one night stand
SL
Storytel
Reset day and today is the biggest
Another Company Call netcompany jag kör
Unsystematic
Are closing another
Trekanten
Kompress
Rainbow Six Siege
Det var synd
Eurosko
And the company has actually
Binder developer of the latest poll
Eniro
Candi ass
Change the strategy that äcklig on Ice working Channel
Search for themselves in a more open source
Fridas test with me to do
Isschema Kungsbacka
Sodastream
Skicka SMS a picture in the room
Sauber
Alltså vi känner vatten
Ännu
Mix me happy that over tree
Polisen friday night is a pinch of inspiration
Only sett
P******
Pappa
Kostnadsställe
4chan
Så kostnad Euro accident campingplats i Ready To Break Free
This is happening
Och jag så hett som
Vi hade few smala Company
Överkalixmål
Tangentbord Android
100 % hos oss så det här
Reading about everything P3
Willy's
Slices
Psykolog omdöme Karlsson
Gudinna
Winning World War 2
Arvid
Champions League
Okej
Yes
Open Snapchat
Discussion like time for We have touched on Dillon
Att
Start Continue talking about the relationship to the supplier Sanders
How are you experiencing
I am working with the Stars
Italienare
That's ögonhälsan If you're dealing with a mission the prisoner
90 grader måste det vara i bälte
Ja det har jag inte skrivit in I like to say that again I station
Ja men det gör vi Snap to build saker i so
We are well aware this in The Team
For example we use to Run
Man jag är bäst
Where we invited the
QuizMe
Where we invited Dean
Players the Market Players And We Told them again
Golden Windows
Säg något inte Säg hej
You need to understand what the Lies in order to protect yourself to Punish in the same
The Public administration site
Så
Of course we need to for them to instruction and
To provide tutuapp
Måste Power platform centralbank från sin avbild by central public administration
We are right now Publishing D80 ice
Standerths på Elisa din Travis Anders
So we try to travel
EP
I Know Where you live
Lake of public administration for all publications to interact with them
Of course we need to
Sätt som standard Ring brandombud final
Use the international standards på dining place in the canonical system and
Allow These wires to use those creepy Isaac Marcus
Something they were doing Direction intro problem
Also True wireless and wires when they build a new South Wales new Solution that
Så
Little by little We are going bad
We are seeing some of them that I really Just fine
Easily switching insane Ok This is the way to go we have to go
Design
If you want to work with answers and that's it will go This Way
Well some other girl trying to understand Which is the best business model of bitterness so
Junior
Sms:a Rasmus
Different possibilities different and Architecture of
Principles of communism
Where do I going this way our eyes meaning
Most of them at least the most important and understood the This is the low in place
Baby Can not Stay still get the move on mood for dinner
How to
Diggiloo
The Reality of the world
Adx How are you experience any type of loving from War
Larger primary
Så du känner
Really at least a Wizard some large
Vendors that are really
Gå in Directions ossein releasing
Big important pieces of South
But Of course it's not gonna be
Transformers self We need to really understand everything
The same to you
Dinosaurier
The Maze i USA
Disruptor of the year
The Beatles
Provided the Tools to understand this is not something that will break their business Model
The new Possible
The new opportunities offered by or Die
Vad är bixby
For example is something that we introduce and I didn't tell you before
I need something That's what the french laundry
Douglas before we don't
Just det
Katalog
Open source Software developed by public administration
I Will Survive the action is the third party
To Mark Benders
Open source after build
Vilken tabell
You inside of work work
Open source
Saab The Public administration Riverdale Reggie compared to the ass men
Jätte taking the consideration that
Open source up before considering diplopi
Så agenter suction in our Purple in our website
We can say if you have
Public
You have open source Software can be of Interest
Workout
Check big quality
So you're welcome to the rhythm to make the public administration aware of the Season 8
Show me something the world going were doing daddy
New
Business
Bastian
Brother Walker Spectre How are you working in the US
Paprika med brasa
Att Norwegian out
Bad luck
SM Count of
Interface to watch the original and Genesis
Hallå
How do you work in the US and more look like
Gös Bastian
Ripasso Energy
Can you ask about
Love me love me again
Expressen.se
Most of the companies that trade of companies that rely on
Bertil
Samsung 16
NDR concentrate
Oliven
Gå vinnande Bella
Simulator karta
Alopecia
Take away Denmark
Ursäkta att jag inte kunde svara
Open Italy Where are you Can you connect to choose to bypass Chopper if you have
Explanation
Rullstol
We have the same Approach and Morgan wichuda
We don't stop believing If there's always
Action trailer
And those Options are
Goodnight
Great Solution
Sometimes
Maybe There's Only one choice and inches
So
When is okay to do
Freight Solutions on the market
Konichiwa
Den Ljusdals IF hemsida ok 2360
Avslutningsfest
Huskvarna bibliotek
Switch into
Kan du starta but the politicians and Upper management within the public administration
Hallå
How do you manage the communication because
But communicating Garrison
How do you communicate and how do you
Det funkar inte den
Captain Marvel
Open source
Open questions to Youtube
Curse
Okej så den här in
Rudi Pell som det
On the skills of the People of the Earth
So if the person you're talking to
Säg Hälsan background in I keep it maybe
More easier the Taylor
Om Because you can go all the details in explaining the benefits
Ahlsell
Take me to you know
If the person you talking with doesn't have a clue about
Den
Gmail
In technical details because that
Candida albicans using our can be before the switch trainer
Is like in Islam
Lawyer talk to me Lord and then I
Quite hard to grasp of the Deep
Så
I will you again with a different Approach depending on the person Without You
Really Right Now we have
Hallå
Person is Golden responsible for Digital transformation
En häst växer
Every public administration
And that is What say our first point of contact
We know there's a person that is responsible for everything regarding
Transformationszon
Majestic procurement butterfly
Anne
Digital strategies original picture strategies and whatever the
The Public administration will do in from here to breathe Five Years
Saw the first point of contact me for Sweden
That version doesn't react
Try to go
Boss in both Directions in the technical Thank you for the other Direction
Audi RS
Top Management
Agge
In this case over leverage is the law so when we talking with top Management
No available
Again
Software
German
Ikey Solutions
We go and use the lower levels
When we talking with other people are more technical we
Adele
Tina What's Playing the Benefit of this model explained
How to know how to interact with the choir
Innan innan opensource
Ja
Me really happens on the person you're talking to try to save our communication
Indie
How to remove the max
Jax different word coach
We have a Statue of
Taking a large and also on to you
Korsvik blackchiina
To have some coffee maker of influence eller makes
Freddys
Din arbete
Det är bra musik så vi have people
En ny position
Responsible har gjort sidan
Travian social and
Sometimes with sexy people have to session Power What time is it
That's one party
Eksem i Kalix
Bikini
Artikelns
Just
Challenge
How to calibrate works WhatsApp in polisen
Organising meetups Internal
Squishies
Jag hoppas ju på att joina
Också
Everywhere and that way
Making a sofa
Anniversary
Bibelfigur Avicii
Tittar vi sen
Decibelgränser
OKQ8 Ljusne på artisten
People with the Curious
Hitta
Men det högsta trappa
Experience any difference in terms of communicating and Building
Culture on the demise
Dimension that
Stadium caesarstone challenge
DB Schenker
This Way
The cheapest
Transformers
If They choose another Solutions in which to our If They can't find
Musical.ly
Coachella
Execute 4
Jag tänkte - 500.000
Matmarknaden 2019
Sodexo
Där som du skulle
I don't have the same but
Nej tack
When the pros and peace
Digitalization h.e.r.
Shoes and bags
Grill
Nmd Jason Helen matsmart politiker
Try to
Why don't we do it This Way using open source
Novita talk to figure out our thinking about the roses
Använda på sig fidget spinner
Sodastream pris
Jackson collaboration
Twitch
What's different Android
Moving to Hawaii
Väder State Park is going to go to the kids appen
First member
Hosting service
Instead
Andras bekostnad
Hon svarar inte
Bilinvest
Är det någon som
Det är mycket från det
Ontarget
Leo Do you want to that because you have original Compton
So
Agenda
I think I think whatever the Rising Sun
Tänd i applied English Where is hoi4 min in my
Sliced
The way to Be careful that all public emissions Are The Same
And of Legends political influence in Subway stairs
Star serie
Resources in other
Mina the location song
So
This is very true in League
Så pizza
It's important I think
What the fuck
Special with Little Miss bodies
Kontakt
That
We are great
The Demand
We were able to serve them better so ugly
Big Sam supplier Sundance
Darling The Wheel of Energy
So
In some cases
Personligt
Aryan Little
Cantec
Pizza It's working I still need ready working right now
So I have ugly relationship with
Sms:a Samuel is that they know Then and Resources
Poseidon I don't have the skills to Maybe Follow the development process
Saw instead of Being
Subway laugh in a single supplier does everything that I want and
Give provide the Single service in
The reluctant
Supplier login
They are gay the Forces They they find other people on the territorial army stationsområdet
That may have the same Island
Hängde kvar men sen den
Rasmus had a day day and more Power
Able to
Open discussion with different players understand how to build a software
How to attach A service provided in the
How to make a Balance better the resource with economic and financial Resources
To have the Production Team
Arne Lamberth
Så kompetent centers
I think
Det
Deer Roll is it strategy
Sås
They should know on a local level
What's dig
The situation more or less
Requirement the Academy the real name
And then understand how to translate The Smiths into
Possible Solutions i avtal quiz
Miniderm Conversation with Wire Sandnes
Unden
Agent
Build a Solution in
Know how to cover that Solution Of The governance Model
Project is always
Albert Ricky special if you if you
If You're never too big
Så
I think Kompetenscenter really Avicii
Whiskey roll Erin discussion
With encoding of spo setlist
No
Better With Me on my shoulder I will see all things with Ball
Again
Stress this over and over again
Doesn't know what you're talking about
Ica whisky to accompany center Sanders Northampton
And you know if you're a Leo
Little Miss party you go virizion counters
Forever
Sporting
Yoga
Betting Radio betting over
Jobbar inom det är men inte jag Men vi kan ta den
Follow you I can be lyrics Because you have to lose
Sågen pizza It's a challenge with
We have the
Clear answer now on how to go Avengers Kompetenscenter Auto
B
Hand sensura Teresa a good percentage of
Of knowledge the competences are there but I think this is
Crucial
I c e What's the weather
Why are you speaking speaking about
Salem
Medication Stop
One thing that I think we have sex with that
Countries that don't have eller support
Easier to look at bara collaboration
Denmark
CNN
Men jag har polisen
Den smala collaboration 15
Refurbished braces
Those ecosystems Can you have a
Next
I don't want this way Justin Bieber
Västerås
Notice that someone ask about
Ring Anna Olsson
Crossboss
Very interesting
Nothing nothing nothing
Bara Du erkänner att det finns en person
In Sweden have summer
Saknar dig
Samsung Galaxy Note 2
En en
Ja men alltså felkörning
GPA
Älskling
Sweden successful Swedish military
Ta inte hem
Men den Den är inte så
Barnvisor från publicos
Monster trucks
Going to have a spade
Almost any question How can we
Movies for with hardware in the areas where we can celebrate
Series where
Framme
Change
And very interested in the public public code.org
Hur får mest bensin
Things we like in the night we don't have a cat
De här
Far
Making people aware that
We have to protect
Älskar dig
Alarm 10
Räddningstjänsten Danmark
Tatuering med Conor någon News
Så vi fick upp det
International ice
Code.org
Formel spene
Everyone but me today to five in the parties
I will
Roger tappat Nathalies försäkring
I think the game changer in Italy has been in the car
Som
Again
Because Most of the time with getting phone calls in administration tell me how
I find software
And this Maybe I really really
Skicka min sim i Sims 3 i en silly for måste vara billig me
People that are in the Pokémon Face in Sunny station
I don't really know much about the bad
Bitbucket Registry
Så
Building a castle of institutional is to say hey This is the national One
Please
Seglarintyg consideration the law is telling you
Was the first step and really were singing a lot going on
On.com
Of course building a color and then make a straight forward special
You say and you say in the morning
Of course This is where working a j station Erika delfin
Sudio
Is
Är integrated into account of over and over again in a strange person
So we are still Building and of course the color
Is nothing If there's not a way to this entry
Black Friday Torrevieja
So what Rasmus saying about the public Enya
Specifikationer tvillingpodden
We will be doing
Work since I Got That
Our department is getting bigger is going so
What we will have people
Will be able to work
Specifically on the Evolution of the papegoja
Specifications so we want We will
Albin kommunikation i all of you need to extend
Det är
Spela the interaction Over The Public road in Northern Sweden
More Insight more feedback discussion in the public and open fashion
And then understand how to evolve and use it as much
I think we are in use
Where can I eat dog food I always med Pitbull
This
Slagen in order to use it see how we can fix it and quicksand
Volbeat let people Love This is not something
Stable study and Written in the Roxbury de cambio ålder
Build layers on top
Thank you let that be the last
Reply on today's workout
We have
Lördagslåda hopefully I will
The package of the status that you have communicated and I hope we will
Vi kan Continue a conversation after this and keep
Learning and exchange ideas
Work
Push forward the guidance and Consent of open source
Nationalmuseum
Grey
Big mcthankies To Your Mother Bastian And Rust
Viaplay
Appreciate you taking the time to
Visa stand
Eurovision Georgia
Experis
And with that
Hur ser sommarbrisen
And The older colleague cemetery bipap
Agios
Soundcloud.com
Jula
Thank you